-=xXSwesubsXx=-
Two gunmen have been shot dead
after they opened fire
in a shopping center...
As many as 80. 000 residents of the city
have fled their homes
to escape the shooting...
Government forces
in the southern Philippines
have launched
an offensive against rebels
as fighting escalates
in this part
of Asia's largest
Catholic country.
A national day of mourning
in the Philippines
after 44 police commandos
were killed in the line of duty
when an anti-terror
operation went wrong.
Two hundred
heavily armed separatists
from the National
Liberation Front
attacked the city of Zamboanga.
The officers from the
police special action force were killed
during an operation to capture one
of the most wanted terrorists.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Philippine authorities now
say the toll in yesterday's hotel bombing
has risen to 146 dead
and 231 wounded.
It is the most devastating terrorist
attack in Asia in 10 years
and the worst ever in Manila.
While no organization has taken
responsibility for the blast.
Western intelligence sources
have identified chemical traces
that are the hallmark of the
infamous arms dealer. Aamir Barkawi.
International
security experts say
the Barkawi family is now instigating
violence in remote capitals
to foster instability
and thus fuel
massive arms sales
around the globe.
There he is.
Kamran.
Raza.
Did Philippine
intelligence track you?
Okay.
Father.
Hmm.
You did well.
Thank you.
We need to discuss
Major General Rahman.
It's your
sister's wedding.
I'm sorry.
This can't wait.
I think your ISI officer
was compromised.
Kamran. all Pakistani intelligence
officers are compromised.
One of our Afghani
friends discovered
a German BND agent
in his circle.
And?
That particular general won't
be very useful to us anymore.
He's been eliminated.
Thought you might
want to know.
Don't forget
his family.
Vengeance
must always be
profound and absolute.
So am I.
I'm very happy.
Pentagon just received target
confirmation from MI6 ground asset.
You're clear
to execute.
Hell of a
presidential race. sir.
Every day
the same damn joke.
Seriously?
What the hell did
they make you out of?
Bourbon and poor choices.
You pick a name yet?
We were thinking Benjamin
if it was a boy.
Really?
Hell no!
If it's a girl. maybe.
Voight.
you wanna
run over him for me?
Believe me. sir.
we've tried.
Baby?
Babe.
Mmm.
What?
Little problem
in the nursery.
All right.
so six cameras. right?
One. two. three.
four. five. six.
What. is that too much?
Yeah. maybe.
Yeah. it's too much.
I thought that.
They're baby gifts
from the guys.
I'll take them down.
All we need
is one baby monitor.
One baby monitor.
right. okay.
And a Kevlar mattress.
Come here.
Unhand me.
Never.
And guess who just got
the next week off?
Oh. don't toy with me. young man.
'cause there will be consequences.
No. no. we're finishing
this nursery.
I can't believe it's
taken me this long.
Paint samples.
What?
Yeah. Oh. I gotta show you these
amazing new paint samples.
Can I get
a shower first?
God. yes!
Sir. Speaker of the House
is waiting.
And the Senate Majority Leader
would like five of your time.
Oh. Um...
I'll take him first.
Hmm.
When is Trumbull
getting back?
The Vice President has three
more days of vacation
and insinuated
considerable violence
if he heard my voice before then.
Yeah. never get between
that man and a fish.
Sir. I got your son
on video chat.
Excellent.
He had his first date
last night.
Mr. President.
you need to take this. sir.
Sir.
Speaker of the House?
You need to
take this now. sir.
This is the President.
Okay. Thank you.
Sources confirmed
that Prime Minister
James Wilson has died
while sleeping in his residence
at 10 Downing Street.
He is believed to have
suffered a heart attack.
possibly from complications
after a surgical procedure
to repair his knee
a day earlier.
An autopsy has been scheduled
within the next 48 hours
to determine
the actual cause of death.
It's the White House.
It's okay.
My mom can come over.
What we are proposing
is that the funeral takes
place this Thursday. the 9th.
4:00 p.m.
at St. Paul's.
The confirmed attendees
are all world leaders.
with the lone exception
of the Russian president.
Well.
no love lost there.
Our Royal Family will
attend a private service
at St. James's Palace.
the morning of.
with 28 other heads of state
from all over the globe.
As per foreign royals.
Prince Albert of Monaco.
Queen Rania of Jordan.
Saudi Prince Muqrin.
Yes. it's a
logistical nightmare.
But let's make sure
this runs without a hitch.
Questions?
And what special requests have
the Yank circus demanded so far?
Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders
part of the retinue. possibly?
That's a
request I could live with.
I'm partial to the Kardashians myself.
as apparently is Her Majesty.
Nineteen special requests
from 12 different countries.
We've denied all of them.
Any issues of special concern
with our current assessments?
We all know about the 350
or so British nationals
who've traveled back and forth
to Syria in the past year.
as we've seen before
in Iraq and Afghanistan.
Of rising concern
is the handful
we believe to be
former military.
Is any of this
actionable?
No.
Very well.
Then we will see off our dear
friend James with dignity.
Give him the ceremony
he deserves.
Sir?
Are you ready for us?
Oh.
Yeah. come on in.
Take a seat.
What are you guys
so damn nervous about?
The Brits are world class.
We all know their reputation.
But still. these are
the trips I hate.
Last minute. Out of the country.
No time to plan.
Are you sure I can't
talk you out of this?
Lynne.
it's a state funeral.
It's our oldest.
strongest ally.
I spent half the night on the
line with our advance team.
Metropolitan Police will secure
the perimeter of the funeral
at St. Paul's Cathedral.
Air Force One will land
at Stansted Airport.
On the ground
it's all Mike.
Touchdown. Then a 12-minute
chopper ride to Somerset House.
From there we take
an armored-vehicle escort
down Fleet Street
to the cathedral.
You don't
seem thrilled.
Well. the British
have their hands full.
It's a clusterfuck...
Sir.
Well. 40
different countries
with 40 different
security teams.
Minimal flexibility
on approach routes.
funeral seating. egress.
Can we make it work?
Mike?
I always do. sir.
Good.
I know it's not great
timing for you. but...
It's what I do.
Thank you. sir.
There's my man.
Mr. Vice President.
How was your vacation. sir?
Son. do you have any idea
the joy a man feels
pulling
a 70-pound king mackerel
out of the waters
around Jekyll Island?
No. sir. I don't.
That makes two of us.
And I'll have to wait
until next year to find out.
But thanks for asking.
Oh. yeah.
that's in the Sinai.
- It's beautiful.
- There you go.
Oh. gee. that's incredible.
I love these things. They all are...
Don't worry about a thing.
We'll be fine.
Doris.
can we have a minute?
Sure.
Oh. you meant Leah.
Right.
Very funny. Doris.
And she tells me
not to worry.
It's only three days.
Yeah. And I'm not
due for two weeks.
The walking away ain't
quite so easy this time.
Hey. I got this.
You go and you do
what you have to do
and we will be right here
when you get back. okay?
You. say bye-bye
to Daddy.
Hmm.
Bye-bye. Daddy.
Bell tolls.
Yeah.
I love you.
You better.
Behave.
Uh. here you go.
Thank you.
You've been hiding lately.
You busy nesting?
Something like that.
Mmm-hmm.
Your idea of nesting being bullet-proofing
the walls of the nursery?
Now. that is actually a great idea.
Yes.
I'll do it.
Well...
That only took two weeks.
Uh-uh. It's no small
thing being a godmother.
I mean. I didn't take
your asking lightly.
Oh. I know.
You think
you can handle it?
Well. I'm competent. brilliant.
stunningly beautiful and
really fucking honored.
Really honored.
Thank you. Lynne.
Big day ahead.
Correction. Mega day.
Morning.
Thank you.
Just your signature here. please.
Thank you. sir.
Gentlemen. ladies.
Today. I need
your undivided best.
The most important people in
the world are in our care.
so muck in
and get it right.
Always. Chief. Hmm.
Good morning. London.
Southpaw
has landed.
Agent Banning.
John Lancaster from 5.
Hey. John.
Bit early. aren't you?
Nope.
We're moving up our schedule.
I see.
The fewer people know the President's
exact movements. the better.
Why wasn't I told?
Nobody was.
That's how
you keep it a surprise.
Well.
thanks for the help.
With security at unprecedented levels
in anticipation
of the funeral.
set to begin just
an hour from now.
this isn't just a gathering of the
world's most powerful leaders.
it is the most protected
event on Earth.
Rooftops in position.
All units in position.
Marine One. Two and Three on
final approach to Somerset House.
Marine One cleared for landing.
Platoon halt!
Present arms!
Nein. it's okay.
Arms!
Thank you.
Stand at ease!
Yeah. I understand.
Yeah. I promise.
Everything is
going to be fine.
Important matters of state?
That was
daughter number two.
She didn't pass
her driving test.
Guess whose fault it is?
Southpaw
has arrived at destination.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Bugs the shit out of me.
Thank you.
Sir.
Thank you. Mike.
Thank you very much. Lynne.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Good to see you.
Benjamin.
thank you for coming.
We're grateful
you could make it.
I'm sorry.
You know. the funny thing is.
James always hated funerals.
Yeah. don't we all?
Get down!
Mike! Mike!
Move!
Let's get inside!
Shit!
All right.
back to the car!
Okay. okay. okay.
Grenade! Down!
Go.
Beast is compromised.
Fuck.
They're not real cops.
Two at the front!
Gulf One to CAT team.
Support on me now.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Stay with me.
We'll get you out of here.
Down!
Shit.
God damn it. Mike.
Oh. Jesus. There's been a massive
attack at the cathedral.
- Chelsea Bridge has collapsed.
- So has Westminster Abbey.
Get me SO15 Counter Terror.
Yes. sir.
Where's emergency response?
On their way. sir.
Voight.
where the fuck are you?
Almost there.
Move! Go! Go!
You okay. sir?
Keep your head down.
Get inside!
- Bronson! Bronson!
- Mike!
Mike!
Let's go!
Go. go!
Let's get to the chopper.
Dean Court.
black Land Rover.
I don't believe it.
They overran everything.
Not everything.
Looking for hard extract.
Marine One. for Southpaw.
Fuck. Comms are down.
All right. here we go.
Get down!
Voight.
Yo.
Let him get
next to us.
Copy that.
Hold him. Hold him.
Now!
Voight. hard brake now!
Drive!
Come on!
Down! Get down!
Voight! Voight!
Voight!
Keep pressure on the wound.
Voight.
Voight. Voight.
He's dead. Lynne.
Oh. God.
Get down. sir.
Jacobs. take the wheel.
Got it!
- Get in!
- Got it.
Mike. on your left!
Get him!
Not really where you
wanna be right now.
Fuck you!
Fuck me?
Fuck you.
We're almost there. sir.
Come on. let's go.
Go. sir. go!
Five world leaders
are confirmed dead.
along with hundreds
of innocent civilians.
in an attack
that has decimated
most of the known landmarks
in the British capital.
Clarkson and Asher are alive.
All the rest are dead.
And I thought it was
too much to hope for.
We just changed
the world.
Plan B. Sultan.
Fate has smiled on us.
Lights out. London.
The generators will kick in.
Ladies and gentlemen.
good evening.
We've asked
the residents of London
to stay indoors
for their own safekeeping
while the situation
remains fluid.
Let there be no doubt
that every relevant police authority
and counter-terrorism unit
is actively at work regaining
control of our streets.
and within hours...
Call Mike.
...we will secure this city
and those responsible will be
swiftly brought to justice.
Jesus.
it's not connecting.
How bad is it?
It's pretty goddamn bad. sir.
All lines of communication
have been compromised.
Both civilian and military.
Shit.
We've tasked
satellites and drones
to get eyes on.
but so far nothing.
Sentinel Drone is on station.
We have visuals incoming.
They're coming up.
Oh. my God.
Nearest quick
reaction force?
Sicily.
Two hours out.
Spin them up.
And get a line to Downing Street
and to Box Emergency Command.
Yes. sir.
Satellite is up.
Marine One is airborne.
Southpaw is evac'ing.
Yes!
Marine One with Southpaw
on board en route to Stansted.
Prepare Air Force One
for urgent departure. Copy.
Copy. Air Force
One prepped and ready to go.
It was a trap.
That's an understatement.
Holy shit.
It's one thing to plan for this.
another to live it.
All right.
well. we're good now.
It'll be okay.
Yeah. We'll be on secure
ground in 10 minutes. okay?
There was no chatter
on this. None.
Something of this magnitude. it took
years to plan. and we had days.
It's a fucking
blood bath.
How did they do this.
Mike?
They only have
to get it right once.
Today they got it right
way more than that.
Fuck. Fuck.
Mayday. mayday. mayday!
Marine Three is down.
Oh. no.
Rooftop. three o'clock!
- You see them?
- Yeah.
Marine Two.
two shooters at three o'clock.
Copy that.
We're being pinged.
Stingers.
Deploying flares.
Okay. stinger down.
- Stinger at three o'clock.
- Climb. climb.
Marine One out of flares.
Marine Two out of flares.
Marine Two.
prepare for sacrifice.
Copy.
Marine Two is down.
Missile lock on.
Mr. President.
we're going to take a hit.
Brace for impact.
Oh. no.
Sir. Sir. are you good?
You okay?
Sit up.
Can you move?
Yeah? Okay. sir.
You with me?
Yeah.
Lynne. Lynne!
No.
My God.
Oh. my God.
Lynne?
Help me stop
the bleeding.
Ben. Ben.
Ben. Get out of the chopper.
Ben. get out of the chopper.
This thing could
blow at any second. Go.
Hey. Hey.
I never thought
you would outlive me.
Me neither.
Oh. shit.
Do me a favor?
Stay alive.
You gotta see your kid.
Make those fuckers pay.
I will.
Box Command. this is Gulf One.
Do you copy?
Fuck!
Fuck. Looks like
we're walking.
Mr. President.
those better be comfortable shoes.
Sir. I think you're gonna
wanna take a look at this.
I'll put it up.
To our friends in the West.
whose idea of war
is a remote dusty location
thousands of miles from the comfort
zone of your shopping malls.
who send your poor to be
blown to bits in our land
or. better yet. murder our
families remotely from the sky.
Your time is over.
We're bringing
the war to you.
Make no mistake.
this is the day
when your world
changes forever.
Jesus.
This is all over
social media. too.
Everybody in the world
has seen this.
Aamir Barkawi.
Number six
on the ten list.
This man is responsible for
more deaths than the plague.
Sells arms to every failed state
in the world.
He has a vast
array of connections.
Terrorists.
mercenaries. corporations.
Mr. Vice President.
it's Barkawi.
Put him through.
I thought you
might take my call.
You understand if I made
it difficult to track.
You have me
at somewhat of a loss.
I thought you would
have learned a lesson
by now about
crawling out of your hole.
I never lifted
a finger against you.
You armed those who have.
I sold triggers.
Mr. Trumbull. just like you.
What do you want?
Your president.
You can end this
right now.
Just hand him over.
That's not going to happen.
Then every death from this moment
forward will be on your head.
Barkawi sells arms
through dummy companies.
some of them
probably in London.
Find a connection to him.
He's probably been
planning this for years.
Everybody makes a mistake.
We have to find it before
he finds the President.
Let's get to it.
Mike. he's a policeman.
Yeah?
Not exactly
standard police issue.
Really?
Oh. my God.
I've never seen
a man suffocate before.
I didn't have a knife.
He's got more ammunition
than the entire US army.
How could they pull
something like this off?
There's gotta be
somebody on the inside.
Yeah. looks like it.
These ain't your typical
spray-and-pray hillbillies.
These guys are pros.
We should go
for the embassy.
No. they'll be
expecting that.
There's an MI6 safe house near here.
I have a contact there.
We go there. we wait it out
and we get an extraction.
Do you trust them?
Yeah.
The fact is. every single one of
these guys is a terrorist asshole
until proven otherwise.
The only person you trust
right now is me. okay?
Come on. let's go.
We gotta
get underground.
These guys
are everywhere.
Let's go.
Stay here.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Raza.
Here.
Or we can do this the really
fucking hard way.
Raza.
Answer me. brother.
Okay.
Raza's not feeling
too well at the moment.
He's a little bit
fucked up.
Yo. what's this
dickhead's name?
This is Kamran.
Who is this?
Hey. Kamran.
My name's Mike Banning.
You are the one
with the President.
Bingo.
So why don't you boys pack up your
shit and head back to Fuckheadistan
or wherever it is
you're from?
You should have let us
kill him quickly.
because now we're
going to kill him slowly
and stream it live
for the whole world to see.
Can you hear me.
Mr. President?
Tell him.
Yeah.
he can hear you.
Here's something
I want you to hear first.
That's the sound
of your brother dying.
Yeah. not much
of a talker. that one.
but I'll bet you
one of your men will.
I'll see you soon. Kamran.
Was that really necessary?
No.
The Brits are compromised.
Police for sure.
Who do you trust?
We can also assume all
communications are compromised.
Anything that isn't secured could
get into the wrong hands. sir.
And Banning
would know that. too.
So how could he even
reach out for help?
There. Freeze that.
Sir. is. is
Banning left-handed?
No. he's right-handed.
Okay. well.
the President doesn't move
without a drone or a
satellite over his head.
Banning knows that.
It's his left hand.
Southpaw. six.
Shorthand for MI6.
Look for any MI6
location in that area.
Yes. sir.
All right. Banning.
You okay?
Hell. yeah.
Made out of bourbon
and bad choices. huh?
Huh.
Sit down.
Take deep breaths.
How many you think died?
I don't know. A lot.
All those innocent people.
Dead. because of me.
No. not because of you.
Because of them.
They're trying
to kill you. sir.
And they've killed
all these people
just to make everyone else
a little more afraid.
Well. fuck that
and fuck them.
Mike. you don't
let them take me.
I'm not going to.
Let me finish.
If it comes to it.
if it's going to happen...
Sir...
Mike.
If it comes to it.
I want you to kill me.
That's an order.
I will not be executed
for propaganda
as my son and the American
people see me on fucking YouTube
for the rest
of their lives.
Okay.
Vice President Trumbull.
it's an honor. sir.
Chief Inspector.
I'm afraid our news
isn't promising.
Our dearly departed Prime Minister
James Wilson was assassinated.
Poison in his anesthesia
and his doctor's body found
dumped about an hour ago.
State funeral.
Must-attend event for Western leaders.
Each one a target.
Goddamn.
And we walked
right into it.
And all dead.
bar your man and ours.
What's happening
on the ground?
The terrorists have
killed 19 first responders
with another 30
unaccounted for.
They're impersonating us.
Our people are walking
right into ambushes.
Say the word.
we go in.
But make no mistake.
we risk turning London
into another Fallujah.
That's the last thing
we need.
the President in the middle
of an urban battle.
Or the citizens
of London.
You're just as
likely to take out
half the
Metropolitan Police Force
unless you can tell me how
you can tell the difference
between the good guys
and the bad guys.
We're gonna have to stand
down our emergency services.
Surrender London?
He's right.
Take out all
legitimate personnel.
Anyone that remains
is a terrorist.
Look. the sooner
we end this.
the more chance there is of stopping
London becoming a complete war zone.
Well. how do we get the
word out to our people?
Air-raid system.
We sound that. people know to
stay secure in their place.
Then we let
the military sweep in.
go door to door if necessary
and clear these bastards out.
Good evening.
Is Auntie in?
Put that away.
Are you
who I think you are?
Unfortunately.
Thanks.
What a pleasure this is.
two handsome men visiting me
on such a lovely evening.
Long time. Jax.
Yeah. not long enough.
Mr. President.
Sir. Jacquelin.
MI6's finest.
Don't fuck with her.
Hello.
Hmm.
The phones are down.
That said.
it did allow us to pick up this.
Mr. President. Banning.
I hope this finds you well.
Mike. we got your message
and I'm sure you don't know
who you can trust.
and all prior authentications
may be compromised.
so I offer you this...
Do you have any idea
the joy a man experiences
pulling a 70-pound
king mackerel...
Out of the waters
around Jekyll Island?
It's him.
A Delta team has been
clandestinely inserted.
By now they should be
en route to your position.
They'll take you
to the US embassy
where an armored convoy
stand by
to get you out of SAM range
and onto a military jet.
Thank God.
Let's get us out of here.
All right.
so who's behind all this?
Aamir Barkawi.
Barkawi provides armaments.
He's a fucking criminal.
Shielded by governments.
Mike. there was a drone strike
to get him two years ago.
authorized by the G8.
so we took a shot.
He survived. We didn't know
his family was there.
His daughter was killed.
Well. he certainly got
his revenge. Civilians?
Well. they're not being
targeted specifically. but...
Collateral damage?
Yeah. quite a lot. I'm afraid.
It's government targeted.
No official support from any country.
It's Barkawi's show.
But he didn't have any problems
finding recruits. did he?
It's the United Nations of
every-fucking-body that hates us.
Who's on the inside?
There's gotta be somebody.
Yeah. you're right.
They've infiltrated
our CCTV system.
And that can't be done
outside the network.
Yeah. but who?
I don't know.
Mike. if you hadn't
moved our schedule up...
Here you go. sir.
Get this down you.
Thanks.
I don't know about you.
but I'm thirsty as fuck.
Yeah.
Mmm.
How you doing?
I was just thinking
about my son.
He sends me
these jokes every day.
It's kind of our...
I don't know. our thing. or...
A little off color.
His mother wouldn't approve. but...
I tell you
something. Mike.
these little messages
I get from him every day.
they mean everything.
You'll see.
Most important thing.
never criticize.
always encourage.
You just want them
to be passionate.
That's what
I always tell my son.
Find something you care
about and care deeply.
That and the golden rule.
Treat others as you'd like
to be treated.
That's it?
Yeah. basically.
What about
all the other stuff?
You know. sleeping.
eating. electrical outlets...
...diapers. stairs and...
That stuff takes
care of itself.
Really?
No.
You'll figure it out.
I think
your dates have arrived.
When did Trumbull
leave that message?
6:13.
Thirty-two minutes.
No way they got here that fast.
Is there a zoom-in?
Yeah.
They're not sweating.
What? That gear
weighs 40 pounds.
They just stalked all the
way from outside the wire
and not a drop
of sweat?
It's gotta be them.
Now they're going
round the back.
This doesn't look
like a rescue formation.
Please don't tell me
that's not our Delta team.
They've intercepted
Trumbull's message.
Jax. where's the armory?
Go.
Are you not coming?
They'll have
this place surrounded.
They catch us in the open.
we're done.
But they're not
looking for you.
Go. Find the mole.
Right. The wheels are in
the garage downstairs.
All right. point this end
towards the bad guy.
This is not good. Mike.
Stay in here.
Stay down.
And if anybody but me opens that door.
you empty that into them.
What if you
don't come back?
You're fucked.
Mike.
Don't jinx me.
That was inspiring.
I was wondering when you were
gonna come out of the closet.
That's not funny.
We're almost
out of this. sir.
I have another
mile in me. Mike.
Okay. let's go.
God bless MI6.
I'll drive. you shoot.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
We have a mole.
I know.
Well. any ideas?
Someone high up with
access to everything.
routes.
security protocols.
emergency services.
Jacquelin.
what brings you here?
Do we have
the embassy covered?
Affirmative. brother.
Double the men. I want every
single man on that perimeter.
Shit. The car's bullet-proof.
not politician-proof.
Hey. I'm the President
of the United States.
I haven't driven a car in six years.
What do you want?
Fuck. Take a left.
Where we going. Mike?
Embassy.
Embassy? You said
they're expecting that.
They are. but we are
shit out of options.
Take a right.
Mr. Vice President. you wanted
us to find Barkawi's mistake.
Take a look at this.
Of the 119 know Barkawi front
companies he's used in the past...
Twenty-eight have been located in the UK.
11 in London proper.
Well. that's not news.
But it's a baseline.
Now. every entity
he's ever used in the past
followed a very rough
communication pattern except...
No known
communication in or out ever.
Well. that's
under construction.
No one lives
or works there.
That's why this is
particularly interesting.
I had my NSA analyst take a
peek at the power usage.
Through the roof for
the last three weeks.
Pretty odd. considering nobody
lives or works there.
Central London.
Right under
our bloody noses.
Tell SAS that we're gonna
make a house call.
Right.
It doesn't feel right.
Slow.
Left.
Okay. stop.
This don't
look good. Mike.
There's no way to dress this up. sir.
It isn't good.
Could be worse.
We could be walking.
Attaboy.
Don't stop for anyone.
Fuck!
Are we clear?
Yeah.
We fucking made it.
We did it. We did it.
Mike!
Where is he?
Where the fuck is he?
Where'd they take him?
Work site.
Broadwick and Lexington.
Stop. He's done.
Leave him.
Come on. Back off.
Take it easy.
You've gotta be Banning.
Will Davies.
Captain 22. SAS.
Trumbull sent us.
Code. Jekyll Island.
President Asher
has just been taken
and these assholes intend
to publicly execute him.
We know. At 8:00 p.m..
it's all over the Internet.
We'll take care of it.
Move up.
Hey. hey. wait.
Look. we can't let
you come with us. mate.
How many times have you
saved this man's ass?
Now. I'm gonna go
get him
and you can either kill me
or you can come with me.
but it ain't gonna go
any other way.
After you.
CCTV's back up.
What did you do?
Disabled the
authorization code
that shut down
the CCTV systems.
They've been watching us using
our own surveillance systems.
Wait.
What authorization code?
You should be thankful.
How many men get to
experience their death
witnessed
by billions live?
You are going
to go down in history.
I'm not the only one
who's gonna die today. Kamran.
Box Command.
Banning.
Mike Banning?
Chief Inspector Hazard. Scotland Yard.
Hold your position.
Our military will be on your
location in 20 minutes.
No. sir. The President's
gonna be dead in 10.
You don't understand.
We have NSA imagery
of where you're going.
It's their base
of operations.
There are nearly a hundred
terrorists in there.
Yeah?
Well. they should
have brought more men.
All right. Things are
gonna get sporty.
Just watch your balls.
Will do.
RPG!
Two o'clock clear!
Move up!
Okay. fuck that.
They're dug in like
ticks on a dog's arse.
We can't storm that building
with a force this small.
Yeah. They'd kill the President
the second we tried.
Yeah.
All right.
call Box Command.
Make sure the utilities here
are isolated and switched on.
You sound like
a man with a plan.
See the generator?
Yeah.
Let's poke out their eyes.
Generator. 12 o'clock.
Fuck.
What happened?
Power supply
was just cut.
Get the emergency
generators up. Come on!
Mike.
This is
what we've got.
This is a three-story building.
The entrance point is here.
There are two stairwells.
one here and one here.
We believe the President's
being held in this room
on the second floor.
Hold your position.
I need you to hit this building
with everything you got.
You got it. Keep them busy.
I'll sneak in solo.
Take that.
Do not touch that button
until I tell you.
Are you fucking crazy?
Yeah. Wish me luck.
Don't shoot me.
They are almost here.
Why don't you just kill him now?
No. The whole world
has to see this.
You hear that. Kamran?
That's the sound of inevitability.
I'm going
to kill you live.
but that doesn't mean you
can't suffer privately first.
Look at me!
I held my sister as
she died in my arms.
We're all monsters.
Mr. President.
I won't justify your insanity to
make you feel better about yourself.
Shoot him!
Almost.
Power is back. We're waiting for
the Internet connection.
Come on. come on.
Technology.
Only as good as the dumb
shits who are using it.
How long?
Seconds.
We're live now.
Okay.
Say hello to the world.
Mr. President.
Any last words.
Mr. President?
I do solemnly swear that I
will faithfully execute
the office of the President of
the United States...
Son of a bitch.
...United States...
...and will to the best of
my ability preserve. protect
and defend...
Oh. my God.
I'm not watching this.
You know what
you guys don't get?
We're not a fucking building.
We're not a fucking flag.
We're not just one man.
Assholes like you
have been trying
to kill us
for a long fucking time.
But you know what?
A thousand years
from now...
We'll still fucking be here.
Mike. grenade!
What took you so long?
Sorry. I had a couple
of errands to run.
Shit.
Does this fucker ever die?
All right.
we've gotta go.
You good?
Let's get the hell out of here.
Go. go!
- Go!
- Go. go. go!
Come on!
Ahhh!
Mike. come on!
Go. go. go!
Damn it. I'm out.
I'm out. too.
Come in!
Davies.
We're trapped!
I repeat.
we are trapped.
Blow it.
Are you insane? I can't blow it yet.
You're not out.
We're not gonna
get out unless you do!
Just trust me!
Now. God damn it!
Go. go. go!
Banning?
Banning. do you copy?
Has anyone found
any sign of them?
Nothing. Over.
Negative.
Okay. well. stay sharp.
Keep looking.
Box Command. No sign
of the President yet.
Box Command.
we've found them.
The President's alive.
Yeah!
Yes!
Did I ever tell you?
I fucking
hate funerals.
You okay?
Yeah.
Sir. I got you.
Mr. President.
Banning.
That all they got?
Kind of looks like it.
Lieutenant.
this could be the missing
link to Barkawi.
I'll get it to Box
Command right away.
Next time I tell you to blow it.
just blow it.
Good job. Lieutenant.
You. too. Banning.
Safe journey home.
If that's
possible for you.
Next time you wanna leave
town after betraying your country.
how's about you steal a car to
take you to your getaway vehicle?
Preferably one
without a GPS.
'cause that just takes
all the fun out of it.
You forgot to delete
your access logs.
Your authorization code's
there. bright as day.
The security cameras
show you logging on.
Just get on the floor.
Do I have to tell you
this is the most
dangerous time
since the Great War?
They're cutting budgets while
the barbarians are at the gate.
The system's failing us. Jax.
It's broken.
You know it as well as I do.
Things have to change.
So you thought you'd
teach us all a lesson?
That and 20 million euros.
Come with me. Jax.
Get on the fucking floor.
John.
John. get on the floor.
Get on the floor. John.
Get on the fucking floor!
Kamran?
Mr. Barkawi.
I thought
you'd take my call.
You think this war.
this war
that you started.
you think it's over?
I'll dedicate my life to your death.
This war will not end.
Maybe you should
look out your window.
Clear to proceed.
Ground asset confirms target
clear of civilian presence.
Two weeks after the devastating attacks
on the British capital.
a new government
has been installed
and the city has
begun to rebuild.
In the words of
Prime Minister Clarkson.
"London may have fallen.
"but it has always endured
and will rise again."
So Daddy's gonna be
taking some more time off.
Isn't that cool?
Yeah. maybe
it's the new me.
Or maybe
the President insisted.
Hmm. Yeah.
He says he reckons
I've earned a few days off.
thanks to you. little one.
Yeah.
Yeah. it's okay. baby.
It's okay.
Yeah. it's okay.
I wonder what you're gonna be
passionate about. Lynne.
Hmm?
Yeah.
Our hearts
go out to the people of London
and to our friends
around the world.
Far too many people died
for no good reason.
There are those who will say that
this would never have happened
if we would just
mind our own business.
Nothing could be
farther from the truth.
Frankly. we live in a dangerous
world and we have few good options.
But the worst option
is to do nothing.
And finally.
we owe it to our children
and to their children
to engage in the world.
God bless you all
and God bless
the United States of America.
That was Vice President Trumbull
live from the White House.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today